Photograph File (Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum Records--Curatorial Division) RG.0008
Library and Archives
- Gore, Martin L., undated
- Gorky's Zygotic Minci, 1997
- Graham, Bill, undated
- Grand Funk Railroad, undated
- Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, undated (Box OS1, Folder 7, Object 12)
- Grand Puba, undated
- Grateful Dead, 1986-1995, undated
- Green, Al, 1975, undated
- Green Day, 2001-2002, undated
- Green, Grant, 2002
- Greenslade, undated
- Grey Eye Glances, 1998
- Griffith, Nanci, undated
- Gryner, Emm, 1998
- Guess Who, undated
- Guns 'n Roses, undated
- Gunter, Cornel, and the Flairs, undated
- Guster, 2003
- Guthrie, Arlo, undated
- Guthrie, Woody, 1979, undated
- Guy, Buddy, undated
- H2O, undated
- Haitt, John, undated
- Haley, Bill, 1955-1958, undated
- Half Cocked, 2001
- Hall and Oates, undated
- Hammer, 1994
- Hammer, M.C., 1990
- Hammond, Beres, undated
- Hammond, John, 1998, undated
- Hammond, John Sr., 1939, 1985, undated
- Hampton, Lionel, 1956, undated
- Hancock, Herbie, undated
- Hanson, 1997
- Happy Mondays, 1992
- Hard-Fi, undated
- Harford, Chris, undated
- Harp, Everette, 1993
- Harris, Emmylou, 1994, undated
- Harris, Wynonie, undated
- Harrison, George, 1960-1988, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 1-2)
- Harrison, Harry, undated
- Harrison, Wilbert, undated
- Harry, Deborah, undated
- Hash, undated
- Hassles, undated
- Hatebreed, undated
- Hatfield, Juliana, 1998
- Havens, Richie, undated
- Hawkins, Bill, 1949-1967, undated
- Hawkins, Ronnie, undated
- Hawkins, Screamin' Jay, 1958, undated
- Hawkins, Sophie B., 2003
- Hayes, Darren, 2002
- Hayes, Isaac, 1975-1985, undated
- Heap, Imogen, 1998
- Heart, 1978, 1993, undated
- Henderson, Fletcher, undated
- Hendrix, Jimi, 1968-1970, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 6)
- Henry, Clarence "Frogman", undated
- Hensley, Mr. and Mrs.Fiddlin' Bill, undated
- Herman, Dave, undated
- Herman's Hermits, undated
- Herman, Woody, undated
- Hewett, Howard, undated
- Hiatt, John, undated
- Hicks, Dan, undated
- Hill, Faith, undated
- Hill, Lauryn, 1999
- Hitchcock, Robyn, undated
- The Hives, 2002
- Hodge, Gaynel, undated
- Hoku, 1999-2001
- Holiday, Billie, undated
- Holland-Dozier-Holland, undated
- The Hollies, undated
- Holloway, Brenda, undated
- Holly, Buddy, 1955-1958, undated
- Hollywood Flames, undated
- Holman, Bob, 1998
- Homeboy Project, 1991
- Hooker, John Lee, 1994-1998, undated
- Hootie & the Blowfish, undated
- Horne, Lena, 1994
- Hopkins, Lightin', 1934, undated
- Hot Tuna, undated
- Hot Water, undated
- Hounddog, 1999
- Howlin' Wolf, undated
- Hubbard, Freddie, undated
- Hucknall, Mick, undated
- Huff, Leon, undated
- Human League, undated
- Humble Pie, undated
- Hunter, Alberta, undated
- Hunter, Ian, undated
- Hunter, Ivory Joe, undated
- Hurt, Mississippi John, undated
- Husker Du, 1986-1994
- Hyland, Brian, undated
- Ice Cube, undated
- Ice-T, undated
- Idol, Billy, undated
- Iglesias, Enrique, 2001
- Impressions, undated
- Inductees 1986, undated
- Inductees 1987, undated
- Inductees 1988, undated
- Inductees 1989, undated
- Inductees 1990, undated
- Inductees 1991, undated
- Inductees 1992, undated
- Inductees 1993, undated
- Inductees 1994, undated
- Inductees 1995, undated
- Ink Spots, 1942-1945, undated
- Innocent, undated
- Innosense, undated
  autographed promo photograph
- Inspiral Carpets, undated
- Intruders, undated
- INXS, undated
- Iron Butterfly, undated
- Iron Maiden, undated
- Isaak, Chris, 2002
- Isley Brothers, 1986-2001, undated
- It's a Beautiful Day, undated
- J. Geils Band, undated
- Jackson Five, 1972, 1978, undated
- Jackson, Janet, 1993, undated
- Jackson, Joe, undated
- Jackson, Mahalia, 1949, 1967, undated
- Jackson, Michael, 1979, 1983, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 3, Folder 6, Object 8-9)
- Jackson, Milt, undated
- Jackson, Wanda, 1956, 1959, undated
- Jadakiss, 2001
- Jaheim, 2000-2002
- Jam, undated
- Jamerson, James, undated
- James, Elmore, undated
- James, Etta, undated
- James Gang, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 4)
- James, Rick, undated
- James, Tommy, and the Shondells, undated
- Jan and Dean, undated
- Jane's Addiction, 1988-1993
- Jarmels, undated
- Jasper, Chris, undated
- Jefferson Airplane, undated
- Jefferson, Blind Lemon, undated
- Jerky Boys, 1997
- Jesus Christ Superstar, undated
- Jethro Tull, 1969, undated
- Jett, Joan, 1994, undated
- Jewel, undated
- Jimmie's Chicken Shack, 1997
- Jimmy Eat World, 2001
- JJ72, undated
- Jobim, Antonio Carlos, undated
- Joel, Billy, 2001, undated
- John, Dr., undated
- John, Elton, 1979, undated
- John Entwistle's Ox, undated
- Johnnie and the Gyrations, circa 1959-1965, 2002
- Johnson, Andreas, 2001
- Johnson, Johnnie, undated
- Johnson, Lonnie, undated
- Johnson, Marv, undated
- Johnson, Robert, 1939, undated
- Johnston, Freedy, 1994
- Jolie and the Wanted, 2001
- Jones, Howard, undated
- Jones, Quincy, undated
- Jones, Rickie Lee, 1989-1997, undated
- Jones, Tommy Lee, undated
- Joplin, Janis, undated
- Jordan, Louis, undated
- Joshua Light Show, undated
- Journey, undated
- Judas Priest, undated
- Juliana Theory, 2002
- Junior Senior, undated
- Kansas, undated
- Kaukonene, Jorma, 2002
- Keb' Mo', 1997, undated
- Keith, Toby, 2001
- Kenickie, 1997
- Kennedy, Robert Jr., undated
- Kenny, Emer, 1997
- KGB, 2001
- Khan, Chaka, undated
- Kid Rock, undated
- Kidjo, Angelique, 2002
- Kidneythieves, undated
- King, Albert, undated
- King, B.B., undated
- King, Ben E., undated
- King, Carole, 1978, undated
- King, Martin Luther Jr., undated
- King Crimson, 1969
- King Curtis, undated
- Errisson, King, undated
- King Oliver, undated
- Kingsmen, undated
- Kingston Trio, undated
- Kinks, undated
- Kirschner, Don, 1970
- Kiss, 1997, undated
- Knight, Gladys and the Pips, 1974-1975, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 10)
- Knopfler, Mark, 2002
- Kool and the Gang, undated
- Kooper, Al, undated
- Korner, Alexis, undated
- Kraftwerk, undated
- Kramer, Wayne, undated
- Krayzie Bone, undated
- Krieger, Robby, undated
- Krystal, undated
- Kyuss, undated
- La Mere Vipere (Chicago, Ill.), undated
- LaBelle, Patti, undated
- Lady of Rage, 1997
- Lady Soul, 1992
- Laine, Denny, undated
- Landreth, Sonny, 1995
- Lang, Eddie, undated
- Lang, K.D., 2000
- Larkin, Patty, undated
- Largo (Rob Hyman), 1998
- Laswell, Bill, undated
- Latest, undated
- Lattimore, Kenny, undated
- Lauper, Cyndi, undated
- Lawrence, Doc, 1992
- Laws, Hubert, 2002
- Leadbelly, undated
- Leary, Timothy, 1995
- Led Zeppelin, 1969-1977
- Lee, Arthur, undated
- Lee, Brenda, undated
- Lee, Peggy, undated
- Left Banke, undated
- Lefton, Melissa, 2001
- Leiber, Jerry, and Mike Stoller, undated
- Lennon, John, and Yoko Ono, circa 1970s
- Lennox, Annie, undated
- Leschea, 1996
- Lesh, Phil, undated
- Less Than Jake, 2003
- Levellers, undated
- Lewis, Ephraim, undated
- Lewis, Huey, and the News, undated
- Lewis, Jerry Lee, undated
- Lifters Club, 1993
- Lil' Kim, 2001
- Lil' O, undated
- Lil' Bow Wow, undated
- Limp Bizkit, 2000
- Lina, undated
- Linkin Park, 2002-2003
- Little Anthony, undated
- Little Anthony and the Imperials, undated
- Little Eva, 1985
- Little Feat, undated
- Little Richard, 1956-1986, undated
- Little Walter, undated
- Little Willie John, undated
- Living Colour, undated
- Living End, 2000
- Llama, 2001
- LL Cool J, undated
- LMNT, undated
- Lockwood, Robert Jr., undated
- Loeb, Lisa, 2002
- Loggins Kenny, undated
- Lohan, Sinead, 1998
- Long Beach Dub Allstars, 2001
- Lords of the Underground, 1992
- Los Lobos, 1988-1990
- Los Sutch, undated
- Los Super Seven, undated
- Love, undated
- Love, Courtney, undated
- Love, G., 1997
- Lovett, Lyle, undated
- Lovich, Lene, undated
- Lovin' Spoonful, undated
- Lowe, Nick, 1990, undated
- Low Fidelity Allstars, 2002
- Luna, undated
- Lunceford, Jimmie, undated
- Lymon, Frankie, and the Teenagers, undated
- Lynch, Brendan, undated
- Lynch, George, undated
- Lynch Mob, undated
- Lynyrd Skynyrd, undated
- M2M, undated
- Machito, undated
- Mack, Lonnie, undated
- Mad at Gravity, 2002
- Mad Dogs and Englishmen, undated
- Mad for the Racket, undated
- Madonna, circa 1980-2003
- Magazine, undated
- Magic Christian, undated
- Malice, undated
- Malmsteen, Yngwie, undated
- Mamas and the Papas, undated
- Manilow, Barry, undated
- Mann, Aimee, undated
- Mann, Manfred, undated
- Manson, Marilyn, 1998-2000, undated
- Manzanera, Phil, undated
- Manzarek, Ray, and Michael McClure, undated
- Marley, Bob, circa 1970-1979, undated
- Marriott, Steve, 1983
- Marsalis, Branford, undated
- Marsalis, Wynton, undated
- Marshall, Amanda, 2002
- Marshall Tucker Band, undated
- Martha and the Vandellas, undated
- Martin, Dead, undated
- Martin, Sir George, 1998, undated
- Marvellettes, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 11)
- Marx, Richard, 1991
- Mason, Dave, undated
- Master P, undated
- Matchbox 20, undated
- Mathis, Johnny, undated
- Mayall, John, 1969, undated
- Mayfield, Curtis, undated
- McBride, Christian, undated
- MC5, undated
- McCain, Edwin, undated
- McCartney, Linda, 1998
- McCartney, Paul, undated
- McClure, Michael, 1967
- McClurkin Project, 1999
- McCoys, undated
- McCready, Mindy, undated
- McGhee, Brownie and Granville "Sticks", circa 1940 (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 6)
- McGuinn, Roger, undated
- McPhatter, Clyde, undated
- Meat Beat Manifesto, 1998
- Meat Loaf, undated
- Mellencamp, John Cougar, 1997-2001
- Melvin, Harold, and the Blue Notes, undated
- Memphis Minnie, undated
- Men at Work, undated
- Mendes, Sergio, undated
- Menudo, 1985, 1999
- Mercer, Johnny, undated
- Mercer, Mabel, undated
- Merchant, Natalie, circa 1985
- Metallica, 1996, undated
- Meters, undated
- Metheny, Pat, 2003
- Michael, George, undated
- Mickey Mouse Club, circa 1955
- Midnighters, undated
- Midnight Oil, undated
- Mighty Mighty Bosstones, 1998
- Millburn, Amos, undated
- Miles, Buddy, undated
- Miller, Cary, 1982
- Miller, Glenn, undated
- Miller, Steve, undated
- Milsap, Ronnie, undated
- Mindbenders, undated
- Mingus, Charles, undated
- Ministry, undated
- Mint Condition, 1997
- Mint Royale, 2001
- Miracles, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 12-13)
- Miscellaneous DJs, undated
- Miscellaneous photographers (2 folders), circa 2000s
- Mitchell, Joni, 1969, undated
- Mitchell, Mitch, undated
- Mitsou, 1991
- Moa, Anika, undated
- Mobb Deep, undated
- Moby, undated
- Moby Grape, undated
- Modern Jazz Quartet, undated
- Molly Hatchet, undated
- Money, Eddie, undated
- Monk, Thelonious, 1948, undated
- Monkees, 1964-1968, undated
- Mono, undated
- Monroe, Bill, undated
- Monster Magnet, 1998-2000
- Moody Blues, undated
- Moonglows, 1957, undated
- Moore, Mandy, 1999
- Moore, Melba, 1968, 1997
- Moore, Scotty, undated
- Morgan, Meli'sa, undated
- Morcheeba, 2002
- Morells, undated
- Morgan, Robert W., undated
- Morrissey, 1987-1997
- Morissette, Alanis, 2001, 2004
- Morrison, Van, 1966, undated
- Morton, Jelly Roll, 1924-1939, undated
- Motley Crue, 1994, undated
- Motorbaby, 1998
- Motorhead, undated
- Mott the Hoople, undated
- Motown Records, 1965 (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 7)
- Mountain, 1998
- Move, undated
- Mraz, Jason, 2004-2005
- Muddy Waters, 1953-1978, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 15)
- Mueller, John, undated
- Mumba, Samantha, 2001
- Murphy, Peter, undated
- My Sister's Machine, 1993
- Mya, 1998-2001
- 'N Sync, 1999-2000, undated
- Napier-Bell, Simon, 1966
- Nappy Roots, undated
- Nas, 2001
- Nashville Pussy, 1998
- Nathan, Sid, undated
- Nazz, undated
- Ndegeocello, Meshell, 2001
- N'Dour, Youssou, 2004
- Neal, Will, 1940
- Nelly, 2000
- Nelson Family, 1946-1965, undated
- Nelson, Marc, 1991
- Nelson, Rick, undated
- Nelson, Willie, undated
- Neville Brothers, 1994, undated
- New Life Crisis, 2001
- New Order, 1986-1993
- Newman, Randy, 1989, undated
- Newton-John, Olivia, undated
- New York Dolls, undated
- Night Ranger, undated
- Nilsson, Harry, undated
- Nine Days, 2000
- Nine Inch Nails, 2000
- Nirvana, 1993, undated
- Noone, Peter, 1965-1970
- Novacaine, 1997
- Nugent, Ted, undated
- Nyro, Laura, 1971
- Oakenfold, Paul, 2002
- Oasis, 2002
- Ochs, Phil, undated
- O'Connor, Sinead, undated
- O'Jays, 1993, undated
- The Offspring, undated
- OK Go, 2002
- Oldfield, Mike, 1992
- O'Neal, Jamie, 2000
- Orbison, Roy, 1966-1988, undated
- Orioles, 1947, undated
- Organized Konfusion, 1994
- Osborne, Joan, undated
- Osbourne, Ozzy, undated
- Osmonds, 1972-1975
- Ostin, Mo, undated
- Other Star People, 1999
- Otis, Johnny, undated
- Our Lady of Peace, 2001-2002
- Ours, 2001
- Outsiders, undated
- Over the Rhine, 2000
- Ozomatli, 1998, 2001
- Page, Hot Lips, undated
- Palmer, Earl, undated
- Palmer, Robert, undated
- Pantera, 1996
- Pam & Dodi, 2001
- Papa's Culture, undated
- Parker, Charlie, undated
- Parker, Graham, undated
- Parker, Junior, undated
- Parliament, undated
- Parliaments, undated
- Parnes, Larry, 1957-1963, undated
- Parsons, Alan, undated
- Parsons, Graham, 1999
- Partridge Family, 1970, undated
- Party, 1992
- Patton, Charlie, 1929
- Paul, Billy, undated
- Paul, Les, 1935-2003, undated
- Paul, Sean, undated
- Pausini, Laura, undated
- Paxton, Tom, undated
- Paynes, undated
- Payton, Nicholas, 2003
- Peaches and Herb, undated
- Pearl Jam, 1991-1995, undated
- Peeshy, 1997
- Pendergrass, Teddy, undated
- Penguins, undated
- Pere Ubu, undated
- Perez, Amanda, 2003
- Perkins, Carl, 1956-1957, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 5)
- Pete, 2001
- Peter, Paul and Mary, undated
- Peterson, Paul, 1966
- Petty, Tom, and the Heartbreakers, 1980-2002, undated
- Phillips, Bijou, 1999
- Phillips, Little Esther, undated
- Phillips, Sam, undated
- Phish, undated
- Pickett, Wilson, undated
- Pink, 2001
- Pink Floyd (including Syd Barrett), 1966-1988, undated
- Piston, 1997
- Pitney, Gene, undated
- Pixies, undated
- Platters, 1955, 1992, undated
- Play, 2002
- Plug, 1997
- Poco, undated
- POD (Payable on Death), undated
- Poe, undated
- Pogues, 1993
- Poi Dog Pondering, undated
- Poison the Well, undated
- Polara, undated
- Police, 1979-1983, undated
- Poltz, 1997
- Pomus, Doc, undated
- Poni-Tails, 1993
- Pooka, 1993
- Poorboys, 1992
- Possum Dixon, 1998, undated
- Presley, Elvis, 1945-1970, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 6-7)
  Access Restrictions
  The photographs in this file cannot be used without approval from Graceland. Please consult Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials are available.
- Pressure 4-5, 2001
- Pretenders, 1986-1994, undated
- Price, Lloyd, undated
- Primal Scream, 1997
- Primus, 1997-1998
- Primesth, 2001
- Prince, 1984-1994, undated
- Prine, John, undated
- Prisonaires, undated
- Pristeens, 1998
- Procol Harum, undated
- Prodigy, 1997, 2004
- Prodigy Experience, undated
- Professional Murder Music, 2000
- Professor Longhair, undated
- PSC, undated
- Psychedelic Furs, 1982, undated
- Public Enemy, undated
- Puddle of Mudd, 2001
- Pushmonkey, 1998, undated
- Public Image Ltd. (PiL), undated
- Puckett, Gary, and the Union Gap, undated
- Queen, 1974-1990, undated (Box OS1, Folder 9, Object 8)
- Queen Latifah, undated
- Queen Pen, 1997
- Quicksilver Messenger Service, undated
- Quiet Riot, undated
- R.E.M., 1984-2001 (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 8, Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 6)
- Rage Against the Machine, 1996
- Ragovoy, Jerry, 1968
- Rainey, Ma, 1923
- Raitt, Bonnie, 1994, undated
- Ramones, 1976-1983, undated
- Rancid, 2003
- Randle, Bill, undated
- Randolph, Robert, and the Family, 2002
- Rank and File, undated
- Ranks, Shabba, undated
- Rascals, undated
- Raspberries, undated
- Rattlebone, undated
- Ravens, undated
- Ray, Johnnie, undated
- Red Fox, 1993
- Red Hot Chili Peppers, 1991-2003
- Redding, Otis, 1967, undated
- Reed, Jimmy, undated
- Reed, Lou, 1991-2000
- Reeves, Martha, undated
- Reflections, 1964
- Refreshments, 1997
- Remedy, undated
- Renegade Soundwave, undated
- REO Speedwagon, undated
- Replacements, undated
- Res, 2001
- Revere, Paul, and the Raiders, undated
- Rhino, 1998
- Richman, Jonathan, undated
- Righteous Brothers, undated
- Rin', undated
- Rip Chords, undated
- Ritchie, Lionel, undated
- Robert Bradley's Blackwater Surprise, undated
- Robert from the Crypt, undated
- Robertson, Robbie, undated
- Robin S., undated
- Robinson, Smokey, undated
- Rockin' Rebels, undated
- Rockwood, John, undated
- Rodgers, Jimmie, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 9)
- Rodgers, Nile, undated
- Rolling Stones, 1963-1969, undated
- Romantics, undated
- Romeo And, undated
- Ronettes, undated
- Roni Size and Reprazent, 1996
- Ronson, Mick, 1965
- Ronstadt, Linda, 1992-1994
- Rosie and the Originals, undated
- Ross, Eugene, 1997
- Round Robin, undated
- Rouse, Charlie, undated
- Roxanne, undated
- Roxy Music, undated
- Rubber Rodeo, undated
- Run-DMC, undated
- Rundgren, Todd, undated
- Rush, undated
- Russell, Leon, undated
- Rusted Root, undated
- Rydell, Bobby, undated
- Ryder, Mitch, and the Detroit Wheels, undated
- S Club 7, 2000
- Sacred Reich, 1992
- Safina, Alessandro, 2001
- Safri Duo, 2001
- Salt-N-Pepa, undated
- Sam and Dave, undated
- Sambora, Richie, 1998
- Sample This, undated
- Sanborn, David, undated
- Sandoval, Arturo, undated
- Santana, undated
- Satriani, Joe, undated
- Scaggs, Boz, undated
- Scelsa, Vin, undated
- Schmidt, Claudia, undated
- Schwartz, Debby, 1998
- Scott, Jimmy, circa 1994
- Screaming Trees, undated
- Seal, 2003
- Sedaka, Neil, undated
- Searchers, undated
- Seeds, undated
- Seeger, Pete, 1946-1979
- Seger, Bob, undated
- Selvidge, Sid, undated
- Semisonic, undated
- Sexsmith, Ron, 1997
- Sex Pistols, undated (Box OS2, Folder 1, Object 7)
- Shadanks, undated
- Shaka, undated
- Shakur, Tupac, undated
- Shangri-Las, undated
- Shannon, Del, undated
- Sharleen, undated
- Shaw, Woody, undated
- Sheik, Duncan, undated
- Shelley, Pete, undated
- Sherman, Bobby, undated
- Shindig, circa 1964
- Shinedown, undated
- Shinehead, undated
- Shirelles, undated
- Shore, 2004
- Silhouettes, undated
- Silk, undated
- Silver, Horace, undated
- Silver Jubilee, undated
- Simon, Carly, undated
- Simon and Garfunkel, 1960s-2003
- Simone, Nina, undated
- Simple Plan, undated
- Simply Red, undated
- Simpson, Jessica, 2001
- Sinatra, Frank, 1923-1965, undated
- Sinomatic, undated
- Siouxsie and the Banshees, 1981
- Sir Douglas Quintet, undated
- Sisters of Mercy, 1993
- Six by Seven, 1998
- Slade, undated
- Sledge, Percy, undated
- Sly and the Family Stone, 1968-1970, undated
- Sly, Slick and Wicked, undated
  Rock musicians--Ohio--Cleveland--Pictorial works
- Small Faces, undated
- Smashmouth, 1997
- Smith, Bessie, undated
- Smith, G.E., undated
- Smith, Harry, 1985-1987
- Smith, Huey Piano, undated
- Smith, Mamie, undated
- Smith, Patti, 1971-1995, undated
- Smith, Rex, undated
- Smith, Will, 2002
- Smiths, 1992
- Smooth, C.L., and Pete Rock, undated
- Snow, Phoebe, undated
- Son House, undated
- Songs from Chippy, 1994
- Sonic Youth, undated
- Sonkin, Bob, undated
- Sonny and Cher, undated
- Soul Asylum, undated
- Soul Decision, undated
- Soul Stirrers, undated
- Soundgarden, 1994
- Space Monkeys, 1997
- Spaniels, undated
- Sparkle, undated
- Sparks, undated
- Sparxxx, Bubba, 2001
- Spears, Britney, 2000
- Spector, Phil, undated
- Spencer Davis Group, undated
- Spice Girls, 1997
- Spiders from Mars, undated
- Spike 1000 S1K, undated
- Spinal Tap, undated
- Spinners, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 10)
- Spirit, undated
- Spirit of the West, undated
- Spivey, Victoria, undated
- Split Enz, undated
- Springfield, Dusty, undated
- Springfield, Rick, undated
- Springsteen, Bruce, 1995-1998, undated (Box OS1, Folder 4)
- Squeeze, 1993
- SR 71, 2000
- Stage, 2002
- Stanley, Michael, undated
- Stanley, Ralph, 2002
- Staple Singers, undated
- Static-X, 2001
- Starr, Frankie, 1991
- Starr, Ringo, 1998
- Start, 2001
- Stavin Train, 1934
- Steele, The Real Don, 1992
- Steely Dan, 2003
- Steppenwolf, undated
- Stereolab, undated
- Stereomud, 2001
- Stevens, Cat, undated
- Stevens, Connie, undated
- Stew, undated
- Stewart, Jim, undated
- Stewart, Rod, 1971, 1991, undated
- Sting, undated
- Stoddart, John, 2003
- Stone, Robin, undated
- Stone Temple Pilots, undated
- Story, undated
- Story of the Year, 2003
- Streisand, Barbra, 1997-2001
- Styx, undated
- Sub.bionic, undated
- Sugar Ray, undated
- Sugarhill Gang, undated
- Sunny Land Slim, undated
- Sunnyside Boys, undated
- Superdeluxe, 1997
- Supertramp, undated
- Supremes, undated
- Surface, undated
- Sutcliffe, Stuart, undated
- Swallows, undated
- Swan Silvertones, undated
- Sweat, Keith, undated
- Swirl 360, undated
- T. Rex, undated
- T-Ride, 1992
- Taj Mahal, circa 1970s-1990s
- Take 6, 2002
- Talk Talk, undated
- Talking Heads, 1977-1988
- Tatnall, Bill, 1935
- Tatum, Art, undated
- Taylor, Dallas, undated
- Taylor, James, undated
- Taylor, Livingston, undated
- Teagarden, Jack, undated
- Television, 1982, undated
- Temptations, undated
- Tenacious D, undated
- Tex, Joe, undated
- Texas, undated
- Textones, undated
- Tha Liks, undated
- Thalia, undated
- Tharpe, Sister Rosetta, 1940, 1957, undated
- They Might Be Giants, undated
- Thomas, B.J., undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 11)
- Thomas, Carla, undated
- Thomas, Clara, 1998
- Thomas, Rufus, undated
- Thompson, Richard, 1993
- Thompson Twins, undated
- Thornton, Willie Mae "Big Mama", undated
- Three Degrees, undated
- Three Dog Night, undated
- Three Doors Down, undated
- Tiffany, 1989
- Till, Sonny, and his Orioles, undated
- Time, 1999
- Toad the Wet Sprocket, undated
- Toadies, 2001
- Tokens, undated
- Tonic, undated
- Tosh, Peter, undated
- Toto, 1998
- Toussaint, Allen, undated
- Townsend, Henry, undated
- Traffic, undated
- Train, 2001
- Trammps, undated
- Transister, 1997
- Trapt, 2002
- Traveling Wilburys, undated
- Travis, 2000
- Travolta, John, 1976-1980
- Treponem, Pal, 1997
- Trina, undated
- Trin-i-tee 5:7, 1999
- Triumph, undated
- Troggs, undated
- Turner, Ike and Tina, undated
- Turner, Joe, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 12)
- Turner, Roger, undated
- Turrentine, Stanley, undated
- Turtles, undated
- Twelve Trees, undated
- Twista, undated
- Twisted Sister, undated
- Two, 1998
- U2, 1982-1997, undated
- UB40, undated
- U Boat, undated
- Ultramarine, undated
- Uncle Tupelo, 1987-1994
- Unidentified people, 1937-1941, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 15-19, Folder 6, Object 20-24)
- Unidentified places, 1939-1941, 2001, undated
- Union Underground, 2002
- Unit 4 Plus 2, undated
- Unwritten Law, 1998, 2001
- Upton, Pat, 1993
- Uptown Rhythm Kings, 1990
- US3, 1993
- Used, 2002, undated
- Vac, Ricky, and the Rock-a-ways, 1960-1961, undated
- Vai, Steve, undated
- Valens, Ritchie, undated
- Valli, Frankie, undated
- Van Halen, 1986-1993, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 16)
- Vandross, Luther, undated
- Vanilla Fudge, undated
- Vaughan, Jimmie, 1998
- Vaughan, Stevie Ray, 1982, 1985, undated
- Vaughan, Sarah, 1945-1963, undated
- Vega, Suzanne, 2001
- Velvelettes, undated
- Ventures, undated
- Vincent, Gene, 1956-1963, undated
- Violent Femmes, undated
- Vova Nova, 1992
- Wade, 1998
- Wailders Band, undated
- Wainwright, Rufus, 2001-2002
- Waite, John, 1997
- Waits, Tom, 1982, undated
- Walker, Joe Louis, undated
- Walker, Junior, and the All Stars, undated (Box OS1, Folder 6, Object 14)
- Walker, Mike, 2001
- Walker, T-Bone, undated
- Waller, Fats, undated
- Wallflowers, 2000
- Walsh, Joe, 1998, undated
- Ward, Billy, and the Dominoes, undated
- Ward Brothers, undated
- Ward, Clara, undated
- Ward, Fields, 1937
- Wash, Martha, undated
- Washington, Dinah, 1950-1955, undated
- Wasp, 1986
- Wasserman, Bob, and Bob Weir, undated
- Waters, Ethel, 1935-1952, undated
- WDIA (Memphis, TN radio station), 1950
- Weather Report, undated
- Weavers, 1955
- Webb, Jimmy, undated
- Ween, undated
- Weezer, 2001
- Weider, Jim, undated
- Weill, Kurt, undated
- Wells, Junior, 1988, undated
- Wells, Kitty, and the Tennessee Moutain Boys, undated
- Wells, Mary, undated
- Welz, Joey, undated
- Wenner, Jann, undated (Box OS1, Folder 8, Object 13)